https://www.geopolymer.org/about/legal-terms/

Skip to content
MenuScience / ProductsScienceApplicationsArchaeologyLibrary / PapersBooks / TutorialVideoFAQConferencesGeopolymer CampWebinarConferencesShopNewsContact Search
Search for:
Science / ProductsScienceApplicationsArchaeologyLibrary / PapersBooks / TutorialVideoFAQConferencesGeopolymer CampWebinarConferencesShopNewsContactLicence to use this web siteWe authorize:The reproduction and representation as a private copy or for educational and research purposes (scientific papers) without any lucrative use.This, provided you always give credit to the Geopolymer Institute. The source must be clearly indicated in the same way as in your document (i.e. in the caption of a figure or image, a quotation reference for text).The scientific terminology must be used properly, for example: geopolymeric materials, geopolymeric binders, geopolymeric cements, poly(sialate), instead of the general terms such as inorganic, mineral polymer, alkali-activated, or any non standard new acronyms.Establishing of a hyper-link, without frame, to the home page or a category page, or a single page.We forbid:Any other reproduction and representation of any part of this website without our written approval, even for non commercial purpose.You may not alter, transform, or build upon any part of this website.Any of these conditions can be waived if you get written permission from the Geopolymer Institute. It is sometimes very easy to get by writing a simple e-mail.If some people, institutions, companies or other groups are breaching this licence, infringing this website content, we will publish their names here in addition to a possible prosecution.TrademarksJoseph Davidovits put the word GEOPOLYMER (its english spelling) in the Public Domain. It means that everybody can freely use this word in scientific papers, for commercial or non-commercial purpose without any authorization. However, no-one can register this word alone in any country.The radical GEOPOLY® is a registered trademark filed on 21 august 1979 at INPI, Paris, France, ref. # 1 700 by Joseph Davidovits. Only valid in France. Record number: 1 105 493, classification: 1 and 19.The trademark Géopolymère® (the French spelling) is an international trademark registered on 15 march 1990 OMPI/WIPO, ref. # 548 387 by Joseph Davidovits, classification: 1, 17, 19, and 21. Origin France, 5 november 1986, 822 376 / 1 378 923.Publication serviceAll the website content are provided by the Geopolymer Institute for information only. They do not create any commitment on behalf of the Geopolymer Institute. The information contained on the Geopolymer Institute web server are not contractual. They can be modified at any time and the Geopolymer Institute will not be liable for that.The publication director is: Institut Géopolymère Pr. Joseph Davidovits 16, rue Galilée – 02100 Saint-Quentin – France Ph.: 0323676988 E-mail – Web: www.geopolymer.org Non-profit organization registered in France SIRET: 502 751 647 00020 — APE: 8559A — Euro Tax ID: FR13502751647 — RNA: W023000688The Web site host is: SAS OVH 140 quay of Sartel 59100 Roubaix, France Tel.: 0899701761 – www.ovh.comRegistered dataWeb site declared at the CNIL (French National Comission Computer and Liberty, Paris) under the ref. 560320 on 21 january 1998, and updated on 3 february 2005 under the ref. 1071569. You can apply your right to access information concerning you by asking the registered office.The Geopolymer Institute is a not for profit association dedicated to the promotion of the geopolymer science, registered at Saint-Quentin, in France on 7 may 1979, under this reference: Journal Officiel, N° 121, 26 mai 1979, page 4444 — Répertoire National des Associations : W023000688Privacy statementLast update: 25 May 2018What personal data we collect and how we use itWe collect information about you by online forms, contact, download, registration for an event organized by us, and during the checkout process on our online store.While you visit our online store, we will track:Products you’ve viewed: we will use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewed Location, IP address and browser type: we will use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shippingShipping address: we will ask you to enter this so we can, for instance, estimate shipping before you place an order, and send you the order!We will also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you are browsing our site.When you purchase from us, we will ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and optional account information like username and password. We will use this information for purposes, such as, to:Send you information about your account and orderRespond to your requests, including refunds and complaintsProcess payments and prevent fraudSet up your account for our storeComply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxesImprove our store offeringsSend you marketing messages, if you choose to receive themIf you create an account, we will store your name, address, email and phone number, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.E-mail addressAny e-mail address we collect by online forms, contact, download, registration for an event organized by us, online shop, etc. will be added to our mailing list. To keep you informed from time to time (usually 6 to 8 times a year) of news and other things we offer, we use a mass mailing service. You can unsubscribe at any time from this service. We will not transmit to third parties (namely partners or affiliates) our mailing list and your e-mail address. Further details are described below.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsWe consider all messages received as confidential because they may contain information that is privileged and exempt from disclosure.CookiesOur web host OVH is using cookies valid for one hour for performance purposes. We do not control them. Please, check OVH.com privacy statement to know more. You are free to delete these cookies.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWe use the web service Google Analytics to compute anonymous statistics and web audience. They may use a cookie for that, but we do not control it. Please, check Google Analytics privacy statement to know more. You are free to refuse and delete these cookies.Our webhost use the Apache webserver logs to compute general statistics and web audience. The Apache webserver logs are stored in the webhost’s datacenters in France, they include your IP address, and can be searchable with a password protected access.Who on our team has accessMembers of our team have access to the information you provide us. For example, both Administrators and Shop Managers can access:Order information like what was purchased, when it was purchased and where it should be sent,Customer information like your name, email address, and billing and shipping information,Our team members have access to this information to help fulfill orders, process refunds and support you.Who we share your data withFor keeping you informed from time to time (usually between 6 to 8 times a year) about news or other plans we are using a mass mailing service Mailjet.com which manage your e-mail address and your suscription. You will be able to unsubscribe anytime.For processing your order:We accept payments through Stripe. When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to Stripe, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information. They record your name, address, and your credit card numbers is you select this option. Please see the Stripe Privacy Policy for more details (https://stripe.com/privacy).For delivery services (mainly La Poste, UPS or other express shipping service) who need your name and shipping address.How long we retain your dataWe generally store information about you for as long as we need the information for the purposes for which we collect and use it, and we are not legally required to continue to keep it. For example, we will store order information for 10 years for tax and accounting purposes. This includes your name, email address and billing and shipping addresses.If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include e-mails sent by contact forms (messages and download forms) and any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.According to the French law (art. 34 of the law “Informatique et Libertés” ( Computer and Liberty ) 6-jan-1978), you have the right to access, edit, modify and delete all data concerning you. To apply this right, please write us.Where we send your dataMost of the data collected through this website are processed in France except for third party services (Google Analytics) where it is difficult to know at our level.Visitor comments and messages may be checked through an automated spam detection service. Spam detection service collects information. The information collected depends on how the website administrator sets up the service for its website, but typically includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and website URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself). The information maybe processed outside Europe.Additional informationHow we protect your dataAll personal data are stored in a password protected database using WordPress’ technical expertise and hosted by OVH, a webhost located in France. A copy of some of these data, for example those needed to manage our mailing list and our e-commerce, are stored in password protected computer with industry standard encrypted disks. No banking information are stored in our servers or computers.What data breach procedures we have in placeBecause we collect non sensitive information (name, e-mail, physical address, latest orders and files downloaded), any breach will have few consequences. We will inform people with our mailing list of such a breach and will ask those who hold an account to change their password. Get the new edition of the reference book Geopolymer Chemistry & Applications at a special price
Buy the bookNever miss another updateSubscribe to our NewsletterLatest articles
Distribution of sodium and chlorine in samples of Egyptian pyramids
12 Aug 2020
GPCamp 2020
3 Jul 2020
Deep Misleading Publications by Geologists
18 May 2020
A continent is on fire. STOP promoting fly ash-based cements.
12 Jan 2020
#27 Ferro-sialate Geopolymers (-Fe-O-Si-O-Al-O-)
11 Jan 2020
GPCamp 2019
16 Jul 2019 CategoriesNewsScienceApplicationsArchaeologyRoman cementCivilizationPyramidsConferencesGeopolymer CampWebinarConferencesBooks / TutorialLibrary / PapersArchaeological papersTechnical papersJournal GP ArcheoVideoFAQ Watch the latest Geopolymer Camp
keynotes including the “State of Geopolymers” by Prof. Joseph Davidovits. Watch the FREE keynotes videos Learn and understand the basics of geopolymers by watching hours of videos Watch the FREE webinar videos
